diskeeper.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Condusiv Technologies

## Privacy Policy and Information Notice

Thank you for visiting our website (“Site”). Condusiv Technologies (“Condusiv” or the "Company") is committed to treating the personal and corporate information of our Site users, customers, and vendors with respect and sensitivity. This Privacy Policy (together with our Terms of Use and any other policies referenced) identifies how we will collect and process any personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, financial account information, etc., that we collect from you, or that you provide to us. 

As our services evolve and we perceive the need or desirability of using your Personal Data collected in other ways, we may from time to time amend this Privacy Policy. The effective date appears at the end of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check our Site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect and any changes that may have been made to it. 

**_By providing your Personal Data to us in any format (e.g., via email, telephone, fax, or in person) and/or continuing to use any of our services or visiting our Site you accept and consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and Information Notice._**

Definitions   
What Personal Data does the company collect?   
The legal basis for processing your Personal Data   
How does the company use Personal Data?   
Do we share your Personal Data with any third parties?   
Where we store your Personal Data   
How long we store your Personal Data   
Your rights with respect to your Personal Data   
Protecting Children’s Privacy   
Access to your Information   
Changes to our Privacy Policy and Contacting Us

### 1\. Definitions

The following definitions apply to this Privacy Policy: 

“ **Controller** ” means the Company which is the organization that determines the purposes for which, and the manner in which, any Personal Data is Processed and used in its business. 

“ **Processor** ” means any Person or Company Processing Personal Data. 

“ **Data Subject** ” means all living individuals about whom the Company holds Personal Data. 

“ **Electronic** ” means relating to technology having electrical, digital, magnetic, wireless, optical, electromagnetic, or similar capabilities. 

“ **Person** ” means a natural person, corporation, association, organization, partnership, or other legal entity. 

“ **Personal Data** ” means information (whether stored Electronically or in paper-based filing systems) relating to a living individual who can be identified from that data (or from that data and other information in our possession). Personal Data can be factual (such as a name, address, email address, company where you work. Condusiv does not typically collect sensitive data. 

“ **Processing** ” is any activity that involves use of the Personal Data. It includes, without limitation, obtaining, recording or holding the Personal Data, or carrying out any operation or set of operations on the Personal Data including organizing, amending, retrieving, using, disclosing, erasing or destroying it. Processing also includes transferring Personal Data to third parties. 

" **Sensitive Personal Data** " is Personal Data that reveals a person’s racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership; biometric or genetic information; or information about a person’s health, sex life or sexual orientation; criminal records or suspected criminal activity. This Sensitive Personal Data will be handled with extra care as further described in this Policy. Condusiv does not typically collect sensitive personal data from public. 

### 2\. What Personal Data does the company collect? 

You can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Data. But in some circumstances, we may request, and you may submit Personal Data, which may include: 

2.1 **Information you give us:**

You can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Data. But in some circumstances, we may request, and you may give us Personal Data by filling in forms on our Site, or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise. This Personal Data may include: 

  * contact information, such as your name, postal address, telephone number, and email address;
  * employment information, such as title, division, and current employer;
  * financial information, such as credit card and account information; 
  * for job applicants, additional personal information such as a resumé or C.V., education history, security clearance history and status, citizenship information, and position sought, as applicable;

When considering an individual for employment, additional Personal Data may be collected, as set forth in our Employee Privacy Policy. 

2.2 **Information we collect about you**

When you visit our Site, our web server automatically collects the following information: 

  * Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), pages on our Site you viewed; page response times, download errors, duration of page visits, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.
  * Analytics: We use Google Analytics to measure and evaluate access to and traffic on the Public Area of the Site and create user navigation reports for our Site administrators. Google operates independently from us and has its own privacy policy, which we strongly suggest you review. Google may use the information collected through Google Analytics to evaluate Users' and Visitors’ activity on our Site. For more information, see Google Analytics Privacy and Data Sharing. We take measures to protect the technical information collected by our use of Google Analytics. The data collected will only be used on a need to know basis to resolve technical issues, administer the Site and identify visitor preferences; but in this case, the data will be in non-identifiable form. We do not use any of this information to identify Visitors or Users.

2.3 **Information we receive from other sources**

We may obtain information, including Personal Data, from third parties and sources other than from those visiting our website or speaking to a company representative, such as from our partners, advertisers, and other services. If we combine or associate information from other sources with Personal Data that we collect, we will treat the combined information as Personal Data in accordance with this Policy. 

2.4 **Cookies**

A cookie is a text file that our Site transfers to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes and to enhance the quality of your visit to our Site. We use cookies to personalize our Site for you and to collect aggregate information about the Site usage by all of our users. We use some personal info regarding customers logging into their account with us. 

Cookies enable us to identify your device. We use cookies that are strictly necessary to enable you to move around the site or to provide certain basic features. We use cookies to enhance the functionality of the website by storing your preferences, for example. We also use cookies to help us to improve the performance of our website to provide you with a better user experience. By using this Site and/or accepting cookies (e.g., where you are notified that they are intended to be used and you accept their use), they will be placed to maximize your experience and to help us understand how we can improve our Site 

Like many websites, we do not currently respond to “do not track” browser headers. But with most internet browsers, you can take steps to limit the use of cookies. If you do not want us to use cookies in your browser, you can remove cookies from your computer's hard drive, or set your browser to block cookies or to send a warning notice before a cookie is stored on your computer. However, please note that you may not be able to use many of the services on our website or other websites without cookies. 

More detailed information on cookies can be found at www.allaboutcookies.org. 

### 3\. The legal basis for processing your Personal Data

In order to comply with applicable data privacy laws, we are required to set out the legal basis for the processing of your Personal Data. In accordance with the purposes for which we collect and use your Personal Data, as set out above, the legal basis for processing your Personal Data will typically be one of the following: 

  * our own legitimate business interests, or the legitimate business interests of our third party partners and vendors, such as, for example, providing opportunities for customers or prospective customers to request a price quote, download a trial copy or purchase of our products, offering marketing materials or opportunities to attend events, maintaining and promoting our business by providing customers with feedback opportunities, permitting prospective employees to search and apply for job opportunities, handling inquiries from our distributors, vendors, and customers, or other instances where we have carried out a legitimate interests assessment and have established an existing legitimate interest;
  * the performance of a contract that we have in place with you;
  * your consent where appropriate; or 
  * compliance with our legal obligations.

### 4\. How does the company use personal data?

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

4.1 **Information you give to us.** We will use this information: 

  * to comply with applicable laws and regulations;
  * to deliver software products and software product updates to you;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, or between you and our vendors or distributors to provide you with the information, offers, products, and services that you request from us or that we feel may be of interest to you;
  * to notify you about changes to our service;
  * for training purposes, quality assurance, and to record details about the products and services you order from us; 
  * to make inquiries about you for credit reference purposes, where applicable; to perform data analyses (including anonymization and aggregation of Personal Data);
  * for prospective employees, to respond to your job application and process your CV.

4.2 **Information we collect about you.** We will use this information: 

  * to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical, and survey purposes; 
  * to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; 
  * as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure.

4.3 **Information we receive from other sources.**

We will combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We will use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive). 

### 5\. Do we share your Personal Data with any third parties?

We do not sell or otherwise disclose your Personal Data with third parties, except as described in this policy. You agree that we have the right to share your personal information with selected third parties including: 

  * business partners, distributors, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you; 
  * analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimization of our site; 

We will disclose your personal information to third parties in the following circumstances: 

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your Personal Data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets as part of the purchase, transfer, or sale of services or assets;
  * If we sell all or substantially all of our assets to a third party, in which case personal data about our customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others.
  * We may send information to our Partners on any inquiry you may make about a product or service, so that we can service that request. Our Partner may contact you to assist you with your request.

In such circumstances, we request that the third parties put in place adequate measures to safeguard your Personal Data, and that they use any Personal Data for only the intended purpose for which it was shared. In some cases, they will be acting as a data controller of your information and therefore we also advise you to read their Privacy Policy. 

### 6\. Where we store your Personal Data

The data that we collect from you is stored on our servers and in our Cloud facilities in the United States, Europe, or any other country in which Condusiv or its subsidiaries, partners or service providers maintain facilities, which entails a transfer outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to areas where privacy laws may be less strict than in the EEA. By submitting your Personal Data, you agree to this transfer, storing, and processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

### 7\. How long we store your Personal Data

We will keep your personal data for as long as we need it, or as otherwise prescribed by law, for the purposes set out above, and so this period will vary depending on your interactions with us. We may also keep a record of correspondence with you (for example if you have made a complaint about a product) for as long as is necessary to protect us from a legal claim. In some cases, there is a legal requirement to keep Personal Data for a minimum period of time. Unless this is the case, we do not keep your Personal Data for any longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the Personal Data was collected or for which it is to be further processed. 

Please note that where you unsubscribe from our marketing communications, we will keep a record of your email address to ensure we do not send you marketing emails in future. 

### 8\. Your rights with respect to your Personal Data

You have the right to ask us not to process your Personal Data for any purpose, including for marketing purposes. You also have the right to request that we identify what Personal Data we hold about you, that we correct any incorrect or outdated information, or that we erase your Personal Data, unless we have a legitimate reason to retain the Personal Data (such as if we are required to do so for legal reasons). 

Our Site may include links to and from other websites of our partner networks and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites although we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or websites. This Privacy Policy only applies to how Condusiv deals with your Personal Data, and it does not apply to any other company or any other company’s websites even if you access them via our Site. Please check these policies before you submit any Personal Data to these websites. 

### 9\. Access to your information

To check that any information you have provided to the Company is accurate and up to date, to inform the Company of any changes, or to learn what information the Company holds about you, please submit a written request (email) to [privacy@condusiv.com](mailto:privacy@condusiv.com). The Company reserves the right to charge a fee in dealing with such a request as permitted by applicable law and regulations. 

You have the right, at any time, to object to the use of your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes and/or the receipt or further receipt of specific or all types of marketing information, or to object to the use of your Personal Data for any processing activity. To do so, you can direct your request by post to: Privacy Officer, 3600 Kellywood Drive, Austin, Texas 78739 or by e-mail to [privacy@condusiv.com](mailto:privacy@condusiv.com). You can also unsubscribe or manage your subscriptions here <http://learn.condusiv.com/UnsubscribePage-Subscriptions.html>. 

### 10\. Protecting children’s privacy

Our Site is not designed nor intended to be used by children (those under the age of 18, "Minors"). We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from Minors. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any information to us. If you are under 18, you may use our site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

### 11\. Changes to our privacy policy and contacting us

Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our policy and notice. 

This Site is owned and operated by Condusiv. If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions with respect to this Privacy Policy please write to us at [privacy@condusiv.com](mailto:privacy@condusiv.com). 

Updated May 9, 2018
